<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="116"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[KOSTO JOKOV ALBIJANIĆ

  WITH OPEN EYES

GOD PLEASING MAXIMES
      AND PRAYERS

                REVISED EDITION

             NIKŠIĆ, 2022.]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                       CONTENTS

                                                          page
 1. INSTEAD OF FOREWORD .....................................117
 2. INTRODUCTORY MAXIMES ................................119
 3. OUR FATHER.............................................................123
 4. THE TEN GOD’S COMMANDMENTS ................125
 5. PSALM 40.4.................................................................129
 6. GOD, TRUTH, SOUL ................................................131
 7. FAITH, SPIRITUALITY ............................................135
 8. LIFE, REPENTANCE, JUSTICE ..............................138
 9. REASON, KNOWLEDGE, RESPECT.....................142
10. HONESTY, MERCY, GIFT .......................................144
11. CONSCIENCE, SELF- CRITICISM ........................145
12. LOVE, HEALTH, HAPPINESS................................146
13. VANITY, SPITE, DEFIANCE ..................................148
14. LIE, LAZINESS, DAMNATION ..............................151
15. SIN, HYPOCRISY......................................................157
16. GREEDINESS, COVETOUSNESS, ADULTERY ..162
17. AUTHORITY, POLITICS, DEMOCRACY............165
18. MONEY, BRIBE, BLACKMAIL ...............................171
19. POLTROONERY, SLYNESS .....................................172
20. JEALOUSY, HATRED ...............................................173
21. MISFORTUNE, EVIL, MALICE..............................175
22. INSANITY, RASHNESS, STUPIDITY ...................181
23. IDLENESS, IMPUDENCE, THEFT ........................185
24. WAR, FEAR, DESTRUCTION ................................188
25. THE GODLESS, SECTS ............................................190
26. MISCELLANEOUS ...................................................198
27. MESSAGES .................................................................209
28. PRAYERS TO GOD 1, 2, 3, 4....................................219
29. REVELATION 22.12 .................................................227

                                  115]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      116]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

      INSTEAD OF FOREWORD

  This booklet “With Open Eyes” is
meant to show and to warn people (to
open their eyes) about what is good and
what is not. If you read it carefully, it can
really open your eyes to see good and
evil through various forms and their
constant struggle. It also shows the
consequences of following the one or the
other throughout out life.

  I hope the writer will succeed in
opening the spiritual and bodily eyes of
many, so I recommend this book to you.

                           Father Danilo (Jokić)

                                   117]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      118]]></page><page Index="7"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

           ONLY
       OPEN EYES

         CAN SEE
       THE TREE

         OF LIFE

                      119]]></page><page Index="8"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      120]]></page><page Index="9"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      121]]></page><page Index="10"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      122]]></page><page Index="11"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

             OUR FATHER

   Our Father Who art in Heaven,
        Hallowed be Thy name;
          Thy Kingdom come;
            Thy will be done

      on earth, as it is in Heaven;
  Give us this day our daily bread;
    And forgive us our trespasses,
  as we forgive those who trespass

                against us;
And lead us not into temptation; but

          deliver us from evil.
 For Thine is the Kingdom, and the

     power, and the glory forever.
                  Amen!

                                123]]></page><page Index="12"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      124]]></page><page Index="13"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

             THE TEN
 GOD’S COMMANDMENTS

1. I am the Lord thy God; Thou shalt
   have no other gods before Me.

2. Thou shalt not make unto thee any
   graven image; Thou shalt not bow
   down to them or serve them.

3. Thou shalt not take the name of
   the Lord thy God in vain.

4. Remember the Sabbath day to
   keep it holy; six days thou shalt
   labor and do all thy work, but the
   seventh day is sabbath to the Lord
   thy God.

                         125]]></page><page Index="14"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      126]]></page><page Index="15"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

 5. Honor thy father and thy mother,
    that you may be well and that your
    days may be long on the earth.

 6. Thou shalt not murder.
 7. Thou shalt not commit adultery.
 8. Thou shalt not steal.
 9. Thou shalt not bear false witness

    against thy neighbor.
10. Thou shalt not covet anything that

    belongs to the other.

                           127]]></page><page Index="16"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      128]]></page><page Index="17"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

           King David:
  Blessed is the man who puts
his hope in the Lord, and does
not turn to the proud, nor to
those who strive to lies.

                      (Psalm 40. 4.)

                           129]]></page><page Index="18"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      130]]></page><page Index="19"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                6. GOD, TRUTH, SOUL

• God is the truth.
• God supports the truth and gives answers to it
• There is no God’s justice without the truth
• The Lord’s truth is the only undestroyable fortress
• God’s power is where there is moral purity and

  God’s wisdom
• In order to stand on the right side of the Lord’s

  Glory, we should live in the truth of His
• The soul is in blood
• The devil is looking for a human soul as a cat looks

  for liver
• The law above all laws is the Law of the Holy Spirit
• There are no foreign languages for God
• A healthy soul always comes to an agreement
• The truth is the holy house of the Lord
• The truth is the seed of God
• Тhe truth avenges
• By the truth, we praise the Lord

                                  131]]></page><page Index="20"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The truth is light
• The truth and justice are the way of God’s

  governance
• The truth of the Lord refreshes the righteous soul
• The Lord’s truth is a divine wine

• The truth is the perfect law of freedom

• True hope in the Lord brings together those who
  rely on Him

• An enlightened heart can see well even in darkness

• The only truth is that there is the Lord and Paradise

• The only lifesaving truth, way and life is our Lord
  Jesus Christ

• Only the unbribable Court passes a fair judgement
  based on the truthful indictment

• When the Lord sees our persistence in prayer, he
  will say: “Here I am!”

• Whoever goes through searching for the truth,
  they will find the Lord

• Who pleases the stray souls, his soul will go astray
  as well

• When the soul grows thin, it is easily sold

                                  132]]></page><page Index="21"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The most important interpersonal wealth is the
  compliance in the truth of the Lord

• Love is the holiest of holies

• The mercy and the truth are the laws of the
   Lord’s will

• We seek the Lord through the Holy Father prayer
• Heavenly Wisdom is the truth of the Lord
• An irredeemable man hates the Lord’s truth the

  most.
• Heavenly bride is the soul of the righteous person
• To the eyes of Heavenly Eternity there are no secrets
• An honest soul finds rest in work, but to the sick

  one, it is stench
• A darkened soul does not know even its closest

  relatives
• Through God’s help true discernment is attained
• Before the Lord all times are like the present
• The word of the Lord is the only measure of truth
• Paradise is a heavenly field
• The words of the Lord’s truth are the water of life
• By uniting with the Lord our souls are purified

                                  133]]></page><page Index="22"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• In the Church of the Lord there are the medicines
  for all diseases

• The Ark of the Covenant is in the Saints of the Lord
• Тhe Tree of Life holds the keys of the Kingdom of

  Heaven

                                  134]]></page><page Index="23"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

              7. FAITH, SPIRITUALITY

• Destruction is inevitable if spiritual values lose the
  race with material values

• If you are close to God, you are close to your brother,
  too

• Blessed are those who hear the Lord’s voice and take
  care of the trumpet cry

• Man is perfected by works pleasing to God in faith
• Blessed is to build only upon the Lord’s foundation
• Faith in our Lord Jesus Christ brings justice
• Belief is the measurement of the God’s gift
• The faith of the Lord is a guide to man’s works
• There is a great unity of faith and god-pleasing

  deeds in those who are pure in heart
• The Lord’s faith ennobles
• Faith in God without repentance for sins is no faith
• The Lord comes when the God-pleasing ones beg

  him
• There are more believers in Lord than the penitents

                                  135]]></page><page Index="24"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• People who are spiritually empty in their heart and
  lazy as well, usually try to speak as loud as possible
  in order to be heard by the unjust people

• Salvation will come if the prayers are permanent

• Persistence in prayers pleasing to God is the
  foundation of God’s will

• A true penitent for evil is a spiritual treasure trove

• When poisonous weeds cover the Earth even a
  spiritual person can stumble

• He who is close to Lord knows when it is time and
  measurement for something

• He who venerates Saints respects God’s wisdom and
  moral purity

• The one who knows more about marine germ
  defends themselves easier

• Our prayers are the important deeds before the Lord

• A prayer is addressing the Lord

• The believers should not get angry but seek mercy,
  help and protection from God

• In the fear of God there is no hypocritical goodness

• It is a pity for the blessed who dwell in this world
  for a short time

                                  136]]></page><page Index="25"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Spiritual treasure is difficult to attain, but easy to
  lose

• A real believer is only the one who shows his faith
  in acting by the rules of God

• The pious do not shame anyone but do the honor
  to the brethren

• Piety is learned throughout the whole life
• The true spiritual world is more perfect and powerful

  than anything
• The only true meaning of life is in the Lord’s faith
• Neglect of Lord’s faith occurred in Eden
• Christian morality is a community of true faith and

  God-pleasing deeds

                                  137]]></page><page Index="26"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

          8. LIFE, REPENTANCE, JUSTICE

• If the soul and body get rid of the big burden that
  has been held for a long time, then it is the rebirth
  of life

• Blessed are those who cure their leprosy with the
  Jordan Water and Eden Water

• Boon is true goodness
• If we do God pleasing deeds, we praise the name of

  Our Lord Jesus Christ and we acquire the richness
  of eternal life
• Temperance in all blessed needs is pleasing to God
• Life pleasing to God is that one could always do
  better
• Where the spiritual justice governs, there is also
  respect for property justice
• The Lord’s blessing is the rain for the thirsty earth

• Children playing game is a great joy of life

• A good devout and a good penitent – it is the
  righteous one

• Eternal life is life in the Holy Spirit

                                  138]]></page><page Index="27"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Living with a peace in soul is a true treasure

• The law of freedom closes the door to everything
  that is not in the Lord

• Mercy and truth are signs of fulfilling the Lord’s
  commandments

• Confession of sins has a taming effect

• The true justice dwells only in the Lord’s faith

• Healing usually comes like dawn

• Even destiny has its own destiny

• The only blessed justice is that there are no rich
  or poor

• The only remedy for death is the Wisdom of Heaven
• The only secure future for the mankind is to

  become Christ loving people
• Only the best shepherds keep the night watch of

  their flock
• The Morning Star is born only in a pure heart
• The only defense against all evil is to approach to

  and honorably serve our Lord Jesus Christ
• He that hath, to him shall be given, refers to reason

  and fairness

                                  139]]></page><page Index="28"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• When a true and unwavering penitent addresses
  the Lord, he is given the key of the House of David

• To those who are saved from the wicked by the
  Lord, the evil people are not superior any more

• He who finds Lord is freed from the life distress

• Moral purity is a heavenly garment

• Prayers and fasting are a blessed effort with a
  glorious aim

• A beggar as well as a nobleman have to understand
  the sense of living

• The best is the charity done in the name of our
  Lord Jesus Christ

• There is no greater happiness than to become a
  refugee from Babylon

• What is not pleasing to the Lord is beyond the
  pure heart of man

• Deification of the Blessed Holy Spirit is the exit
  from the benumbedness

• Leaving this world in the Lord is the first
  resurrection

• Those who have a pure heart are made of true
  creation

• The appearance of the sign of the Lord’s
  testament in the heaven is the announcement of
  redeemableness for the just people

                                  140]]></page><page Index="29"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Repentance entails confession

• Repentance for sins is a way of telling the good
  from the bad

• Repentance from sin is the reconciliation with the
  Lord God and the way to eternal life

• Repentance from sin means mastering in Christian
  virtues

• Teaching by the word of the Lord opens up the
  horizons and strengthens our faith

• Repentance of sin is the law of spiritual justice

• Righteous people of the Lord are careful of the
  beast and they give it no food

• A lot of them live not for living but for eating

• Everything is in the word of the Lord that is offered
  to us to become His children

• One should direct oneself carefully with the help
  of God.

• Instead of mocking and stumbling, let the mutual
  love, help and benevolent advice rule

• There is no “crocodile” in Holy waters.

• The fear of God and self-criticism is in repentance
  for sins

• What is a peace for the living, it is the peace for
  the deceased

                                  141]]></page><page Index="30"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

      9. REASON, KNOWLEDGE, RESPECT

• A clear mind can be a strong reason to human
  happiness

• It is true that gold is beautiful, but do not allow
  only it to decorate you

• The sweat of an honest, hard worker is a dew from
  Heaven

• A healthy mind is a noble person’s shelter
• He who is shaken by hell’s reality and does not

  wake up, has never met with common sense
• The hair sometimes covers a big treasure
• He who does not consider the consequences of his

  own behavior, he does not know what he is doing
• Progress seeks healthy reasonable behavior
• The one is not a fool who doesn’t know but wants

  to learn.
• Even people alltogether do not know everything
• The New Heaven and the new Earth bring justice

  and joy

                                  142]]></page><page Index="31"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Wide open eyes can see a fatally wounded and
  defrocked beast

• Respect should be met by respect
• Respecting the elderly is appreciation of life

  experience and good behaviour
• Sophia is the true knowledge
• At the culmination of satanic times, healthy

  reasoning and education disagree
• Secrets are the most appealing while they are

  secrets
• Answers to our prayers depend on the truth and

  justice
• Christian virtues are the most beautiful decorations
• Doing as the righteous do is the best self-esteem

                                  143]]></page><page Index="32"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

            10. HONESTY, MERCY, GIFT

• One’s neighbour is the one acting in Lord
• Open-handedness is beneficial
• An honest meeting is the most possible agreement
• The true upbringing is a great gift to the human race
• The only true grace comes to us from Lord
• Only in the Lord’s Peace dwells the prosperity
• He who takes, but never gives back, has a poor soul
• If you give mercy, you will be given it, too
• Childlike naivety and goodness are almost

  inseparable and are very vulnerable
• The hands of mercy caress most beautifully
• Holiness is the greatest of all God’s gifts
• It is lifesaving to serve as an example to others how

  they have been gifted by God
• The ability to know secrets is not a matter of

  education or age
• In the human naivete there is usually goodness

  that is spat upon from the evil and depraved
• God’s gifts are in God’s blessings

                                  144]]></page><page Index="33"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

       11. CONSCIENCE, SELF-CRITICISM

• If the conscience sleeps, decline blossoms
• A man who is pleasing to God does not use devil’s

  weapon
• Where self-criticism is to the good, vanity is on

  the losing side
• Only the true believer will not put a donkey’s

  saddle onto anyone
• The conscience of a man is nothing if it is not

  controlled by the will of God
• Self-criticism in the Lord is the soul nobility
• Who thinks he is sinless, his conscience is dark
• Proliferation of the God’s blessing depends on our

  repentance

                                  145]]></page><page Index="34"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

          12. LOVE, HEALTH, HAPPINESS

• If you spare yourself of vice, you will never be
  sorry for it

• Health smells like the most beautiful spring day
• Health, peace, order and work are foundations of

  people’s progress
• The true goodwill is love and peace
• Sincerely caressing with the soul and body is true

  love
• Love is in the alms and other good deeds in the

  Lord
• Love is not lying
• Those who think they believe but are not repentant

  have the weak love towards Lord
• Not all kinds of love bring good
• Love is the best assistant in work
• Listening to the Lord is the strongest wing to ones’

  happiness
• Happiness is acquired in the company of the

  righteous people

                                  146]]></page><page Index="35"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• There is true goodness in Christian simplicity
• There is tricky happiness in the hills of treasure
• Philanthropy is not in boasting but in mercy

                                  147]]></page><page Index="36"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

           13. VANITY, SPITE, DEFIANCE

• Aggressive and boastful nationalism is driven by
  pride

• What poor people hate the most is the arrogance
  of the rich

• Fury and showing off are the most apparent signs
  of an evil spirit

• Those who are full of themselves are great spiritual
  misery

• Vanity is a contemptuous feeling of higher value
• Vanity in the authorities has a special gravity
• Vanity is a great immorality
• Where there is showing off and disparagement

  there is intolerance, too
• The spirit of egoism and vanity infatuates reasoning
• Proud spiritual cripples underestimate and despise

  ordinary people
• It is demonic to address people with the words:

  „Do you know who I am?“
• The malicious violate the will of God

                                  148]]></page><page Index="37"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The exclusivity and influence of the wise bearers
  of pride are extremely dangerous

• When an evil bride in her homeland comes, the
  enemies of that family rejoice

• He who looks at people severely, he despises them
  as well

• Arrogant people are the devil’s followers

• He who shows off also underestimates others

• Fault finding in other people’s deeds can mean
  extolling oneself and contemning others

• Powerful vain people are often disgusted with
  ordinary people

• Among the darkest are the ones who do not show
  good will

• Powerful vain people respect the poor like a rug
  mat

• The hardest thing is to please those who are not
  willing to please others

• Scientific wisdom is a very strong lure for pridе

• An unjust person is convinced that many people
  are unworthy of the goods he has at his disposal 10

• It is beneath dignity to the holders of the lowest
  humanity to answer any question to the common
  people

                                  149]]></page><page Index="38"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Money and titles are the devil’s favourite tools
• When people in communication address an

  individual in plural it makes the distance between
  them
• The most sensitive are the many when something
  that holds their strength of vanity is “awkwardly”
  touched
• Being defiant is like knocking on the doors of
  trouble
• Disdain also contains a contemptuous hatred
• The one who does not deserve to be honored is the
  one who becomes arrogant
• It is showing off to call upon the so called ‘upper
  class system’
• Where the vanity and ostentation work together,
  there cannot be welfare
• In human boasting there is the face of the most
  dangerous beast’s head
• He who hides or distorts the truth, has a defiant
  heart
• Common reason for rejecting good advice is vanity

                                  150]]></page><page Index="39"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

         14. LIE, LAZINESS, DAMNATION

• If an idle man begins something, he may complete it
• If the relatives lie to each other, is there anyone

  else in the world whom they wouldn’t lie to?
• Spiritually worthless people easily ‘change their

  mind’ by licking the poisonous vomit
• To the chief servants of the antichrist it is not

  foreign to call their action of killing „Merciful
  Angel“
• In evil powerful gents know how to rename the
  greatest curse into the sole justice
• Dignity of the Lord is desecrated by the bodily
  theorizing
• Cursed people who live well think of the poor and
  everything theirs as if it should be the way it is
• By living in disobedience of God, man is leaning
  towards the demon
• It is a delusion to forbid that liars be called liars
• Misused truth can be more dangerous than a lie
• Evil people use some states as a bait on a hook to
  the people they bring distress to

                                  151]]></page><page Index="40"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• A person who praises the truth, but speaks lies is
  the person who offers you bread and poison

• Human depravity creates the impression that the
  previous generations knew almost nothing

• He who does not live in accordance with the
  orthodox rules and thinks they are pious are
  fooling themselves

• A tower made of lies is the tallest building in the
  world

• Chaff strengthens not considering the consequences
  until the force majeure stops it

• Everything of the one who lies a lot is under
  suspicion

• Flattery and boasting arouse egoism, vanity and
  the sense of irreplaceability

• Lie is the Babylonian wine

• Lie is satan

• Lie is darkness

• Lying is damnation

• Lying is the worst lawlessness

• Lying is one of the reasons for the sadness among
  people

                                  152]]></page><page Index="41"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Lying is the law of injustice
• Lies are a pisonous vomit
• A lie is used for causing and developing evil
• A lie is a spiritual emptiness
• Lying is the devil’s goodness
• Lies are devil’s spirituality
• Lies are devilish horns
• A lie is a cursed satan’s lair
• Lie is the true help to theft, and the devil teaches

  such people
• False hopes stem from false feelings and immature

  thinking
• A false repentance can be only a preparation for

  even bigger evil
• A liar is easily offended when they are called liars,

  although they are aware of it
• False harmony among people always leaves

  unsolved problems nearby
• A lie is the most dangerous alcoholism for mankind
• A liar sees a sword in the truth
• Lying stories are a part of infernal directing

                                  153]]></page><page Index="42"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• A lie is nourishment to the disorder
• The lie is the law of slavery
• Lying means recanting the Lord
• Lying is the devil’s welcome
• Lying is humiliation
• Bodily theorizing is the right hand to the damned

  ones
• Everything that caresses our senses is neither good,

  nor it is in the truth
• Thinking of partiality is lying to yourself

• Lack of unmasking liars strongly hinders human
  progress

• You should not confide anything to care to the liar,
  because he can say: “I gave it to someone”

• Inconsideration is the enemy of the truth, justice
  and goodness

• Untruth is an embellished term for a lie

• Laws are not for evil powers that be since they are
  the law

• Lies are to an accomplished liar like water is to a
  thirsty man

• The dishonoured people mainly extol themselves
  by lying and disparaging others

                                  154]]></page><page Index="43"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The arrogant mighties are the image of Aman
  malicious

• An evil person is one who would always like to be
  full up, rested and to have had a good sleep

• Cursed are those who consider the Church of God
  a decay or something irrelevant

• The spirit and the food are at the bottom of the
  stomach to the reprobates

• A damned person enjoys stolen adventures the
  most

• Work is a bloodsucker to a lazy person

• What has been built upon the foul foundation is
  cursed

• To give false testimony is growling at God

• The one constantly praised usually gets the
  impression that he does not need any corrections

• One step is harder to a lazy man, then hundreds
  of them to a diligent man

• Aspiration for lying is worse than an actual lie

• Only a super liar can reveal the lies of another liar

• Influential reprobates are convinced that they are
  entitled to a series of rights to the detriment and
  sorrow of ordinary people

                                  155]]></page><page Index="44"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Lies have short legs, but they catch up on and
  torture many

• The blasphemy of the Holy Spirit is the culmination
  of damnation

                                  156]]></page><page Index="45"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                 15. SIN, HYPOCRISY

• If the only caution against sin is that no one would
  see it, there is no conscience or goodness

• If you are not ashamed of shame - you are in the
  kingdom of sin

• If man does not fear God’s punishment, he will
  not leave sin

• Unchastity is a terrible sin and abuse
• Being a sycophant is a great human flaw and

  feebleness
• The sin from the Garden of Eden is not the past;

  it lasts and is repeated
• The sinful desire is not conceived without the

  influence of the evil spirit
• The majors in ungodly authorities are the mother

  of earthly immorality
• Where the voting is the sordid trade, there is a

  fraud
• While leaders and the rich beasts ruin themselves

  with expensive vices, hungry people dream of bread

                                  157]]></page><page Index="46"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• While an honourable person has collected
  themselves and thought about something, the evil
  can fool them

• The act of conception is desecrated by the physical
  desire

• Evil powers that be enforce the evil and
  retrogression through law

• It is miserable and pitiful to see to whom new
  situations confirm tarnished reputation

• He who tends towards sin easily lies

• For the self-centered and self-sufficient people
  neither the relative nor the God is welcome

• He who finds backbiting stigma appropriate should
  know they could easily get a turn

• He who supports people who do all kinds of things,
  and feigns piousness is a false believer

• Great men who are powerful in evil, know how to
  give honey to the poor so that later his gall bladder
  would become bitter

• Hypocrisy is a fraud and mockery of morality

• False devotees contribute to the church with one
  hand and destroy it with the other

                                  158]]></page><page Index="47"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Hypocrisy is to preach about peace and provoke
  a war at the same time

• It is hypocrisy to believe that it is help when
  someone gives help after he has destroyed that
  person

• People are growing more and more deficient in
  their wish to recognise Lord’s wisdom

• To hate the truth or to blaspheme God is the same

• Many people falsely praise true values only to hide
  their evil deeds

• By measuring the faces of people the corrupt ones
  devise a way to grind the victim

• Many moan about injustice, but repenting is the
  fifth wheel for them

• Many foul people overly perfume their bodies,
  whereas their souls are too smelly

• The sin does not enter a man, but the evil is what
  causes the sin

• It is immoral to present oneself as a benefactor in
  borrowed plumes

• The government branches under the false names
  are more immoral than the evil government

                                  159]]></page><page Index="48"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Some people praise God, but the devil marvels at
  their evil deeds

• The most often curses are the most sinful ones

• With the help of God, you should attack vices as
  with an axe

• Injustice can divide people everywhere, even at
  funerals

• Unblessed teachings profaned almost the whole
  world

• Neither the literacy nor the illiteracy is a misfortune
  but the immorality

• Disrespect is the absence of philanthropy

• No one can say that it is good to lie and hate

• You should be far away from the sermon of a
  hypocrite

• The foul law gives priority to wanton people and
  inhibits the just people

• Depravity is a deliberate action to the detriment
  of other people

• Vice lures the soul and body onto thin ice

• Mocking is the thing of bad manners and very low
  human character

                                  160]]></page><page Index="49"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Mockery often destroys the victim
• To the egotistical greedy it is nothing to throw on

  the net even on their brother
• Injustice from the heart is the worst injustice
• In the absence of self-criticism, constant sinning

  creates an illusion of correctness
• Vain people and egoists are like nightmares to the

  righteous ones
• Tyrannical persuasion is when one persuades one’s

  victims that they have been done well by having
  been done evil
• Instead of adapting to the Lord many would like
  the Lord to adapt to them
• Many reprobates have a spirit of their dignitaries
• In an inconsiderate and depraved company almost
  everyone mocks someone and gossips about them
• Boasting usually creates a false and distorted image
• Infanticide is often the result of fornication

                                  161]]></page><page Index="50"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

       16. GREEDINESS, COVETOUSNESS,
                        ADULTERY

• If a little doesn’t mean something, then more than
  that is going to be nothing

• If your stomach is your only relative, then woe to
  all of your family

• If a dishonest man gives a needle to the honest
  man, the dishonest one is going to expect a crowbar
  in return

• Insane people can easily lose their freedom in
  their greediness and even more than that

• The rich would be happiest if they didn’t have to
  pay anything

• God blesses only the marital bed with just one
  partner, everything except this is adultery

• One easier ‘forgets’ the debt when one is supposed
  to pay it back than when one is to recover the
  arrears

• If there was no greediness, everybody would have
  all they need

• The greedy can take away the ‘skin’ from the poor
  and needy for their favours

                                  162]]></page><page Index="51"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Torture is the devilish satisfactory insatiability

• Self-seekers rarely look for their kins by fairness
  and love

• He who gains benefit from serving retrogression
  or sees honour with pleasure in it wears a shameful
  pack-saddle

• The one who defines property unilaterally is
  greedy, audacious and disrespectful

• A greedy person always refers to what suits him

• It is not fair for the greedy one until everything
  he intended to have is his own

• Greediness is the reason for many misfortunes
  and injustices

• Greed is a great temptation especially for family
  people who are prone to immorality

• The greedy one is looking to straighten a borderline
  where it is crooked, and to bend it where it is
  straight

• A greedy and lying boss never cheats by accident

• To a greedy person it is a speck in the eye when he
  has to help his neighbor

• The greedy can take away from the pauper even
  from what belongs to them through heritage

                                  163]]></page><page Index="52"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• A greedy tiller of land calls the cultivation of land
  into question

• The Egyptian crops are not enough to fill the
  stomachs of the Babylonian locusts

• Uncertainty is an incentive to grabbing and laziness

• Some unrighteous people see the common
  goodness through their own goodness

• Some would like it to be done favours in order to
  transfer their own expenses to others

• Some greedy people would like to sell a thing and
  to keep it

• He who gets to like devil’s morsels and the earthly
  fame also uses the arms of infatuation

• Believers cannot even think of how foul the evil
  people call justice can be

• Adultery is a cursed wine that is honey sweetened
  bile

• An egotistical covetous will bring unbearable
  burden even on his own brother for his own benefit

• Stinginess is a kind of greediness, dishonesty and
  disrespect

• The conditions and means for the immoral powerful
  people to oppress are their powerful states

                                  164]]></page><page Index="53"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

   17. AUTHORITY, POLITICS, DEMOCRACY

• It is insane to expect justice from the authorities
  who are the model to those who lack moral

• The impious authorities are biggest enemies to
  those who tend towards justice

• Wealthy and ruling villains satirize the poor with
  the endless prices of products as well

• The ungodly authorities are the stewards of the
  darkness of this world

• Ungodly authority cannot do without the devil
  by serving him

• Reckless politicians would like to “make happy”
  the people with the support of those who drove a
  wedge between people and robbed them

• The godless authorities are not in favour of the
  pious people, nor the godless people are in favour
  of the pious authorities

• Authority is a test for morality that almost nobody
  passes

• The High Gates of Babylon are the state institutions
  of ungodly authorities

                                  165]]></page><page Index="54"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The authorities know how to make many swallow
  the lie, and then just say: “Let the people decide”

• The worse thing from injustice and crimes is when
  the authorities negotiate what is suitable to those
  who break the law

• If it were not for the support and cooperation with
  the authorities, the usurers would not take away
  from the poor

• In order for an evil person to deceive the same
  victims a number of times they can change the
  bearers of deception

• In order for an evil power that be complete the
  exile they pass an appropriate law

• Current democracy is often a distorted name for
  regression and chaos

• State terrorism is the worst mode of satanism

• When the heads of states are indecent, robbery,
  bribe and blackmail are in charge

• By disregarding political responsibility the doors
  of doing all kinds of things are open to the immoral
  people

• Country abuse is a very dangerous weapon of the
  damned in power

                                  166]]></page><page Index="55"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Evil authorities fools some, reward associates,
  frighten the vulnerable, kill the diehards and
  govern in such manner

• Evil authorities rather steal from the more guileless
  and vulnerable making them martyrs and surplus
  of the people

• Evil authorities can be benefactors to their
  obedients

• The evil and foul authorities find it a pleasure to
  steal, lie and kill the just people

• Prominent ministers of infernal throne advocate
  the democracy that suits them

• Lying power lover gets the impression that he is
  more useful and capable than others, so that he
  can take someone else’s possessions

• When mean leaders live luxuriously, their countries
  go to decline, and peoples’ morality is destroyed

• It is a miserable and sad hope in those who are
  managed by the blackest

• If authorities would defend honor, they would not
  practice stealing

• It is clear to the one who knows at least something
  that political places of worship are devilish
  creations

                                  167]]></page><page Index="56"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• When the authorities introduce anarchy then many
  do everything according to the power and needs
  within and out of the authority

• When the state creates chaos, almost no one is
  spared

• When key setbacks are introduced, other disgraces
  also come to the aid of ungodly authorities

• Authorities defend lies most ardently and vice
  versa

• Some of the most immoral people are those who
  are suitable for the unbelieving ruling policy

• Many political ideas are the means for malevolent
  manipulation and disputes

• As the immoral ones are being established in
  power, so are their insolences growing

• Powerful states have frequently been created by
  violence and crimes

• Moral collapse of the nation is a grave act

• The most dangerous are those crazy people who
  become big in power

• Some of the lying company in the government
  feign piousness in order to deceive

                                  168]]></page><page Index="57"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Some praise their state and the people even when
  they deride them

• Enemy’s rule impoverishes people

• The most ruthless authorities are convinced that
  everything is allowed to them because they do not
  fear God, and people are not ashamed

• Nothing can be sold or paid as expensively as
  political fog

• Dishonoured chief leaders are much worse than
  locusts

• The darkest evils come from the gray eminences

• Those who pass unjust laws do evil observing such
  laws

• To convicted liars lying is their comfort and pride

• The most disastrous infections come from ungodly
  authorities

• Politics is mostly a competition of lies and deceits

• Clapping for politicians has little to do with
  healthy reason

• Political ideas and political patriotism are the tools
  for covering the achievement of personal interests

                                  169]]></page><page Index="58"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Evil authorities usually do what they need and
  what is sufficient for them to be the authorities

• The Damned in power use the state as a shield and
  a cover for immorality

• The honorable people do not find the immoral
  authorities the biggest anxiety but also their
  supporters

• By doing whatever everyone likes the chaos
  inevitably ensues

• Modern democracy is not rarely the antichrist’s
  pillage of human minds

• The poor were usually made poor by the leading
  and rich gentlefolk

• A scheme of foulness has granted authority to an
  evil power

• Instead of support and protection, a variety of
  anxiety and vanity come from the authorities

• Those who were enthroned by the evil powers
  that are independent from them like the fish is
  independent from water

• The cause of cooling of love are most frequently
  from the authorities

                                  170]]></page><page Index="59"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

         18. MONEY, BRIBE, BLACKMAIL

• Bribes and tips are strong destroyers of human
  spirituality

• Nothing alive can lose its way in fog as a person’s
  soul can lose their way in money

• The one in trouble would take a morsel out of his
  mouth to bribe someone

• Insecurity is fit for a blackmail
• A blackmailer makes use of the misfortunes of

  others
• Nowadays, money and earthly enjoyment can

  change even the shepherds into the wolves

                                  171]]></page><page Index="60"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

            19. POLTROONERY, SLYNESS

• Promoting dishonest authorities is not honor, it
  is disgrace and destruction

• The devil enjoys poltroons
• He who finds turning a blind eye to evil suitable

  is a miller in a devil’s mill or is his assistant
• Cunning is а godless wisdom
• Shrewdness and hypocrisy are relatives
• Flattery is an insecure support
• People can disgrace even a fox
• The worst poltron is the one who abuses the victim

  of the one he is flawning over
• The malicious one in merriage is the temptetion

  to the spouse to become their accomplice
• Poltroonish and mocking spirit are usually

  together and cooperate well
• Their victims find it hard to recognise sycophants

  since they adjust their behaviour to the situation
• A sycophant is specially happy when others fawn

  over them
• A sycophant is pleased to be in company with the

  titulars to rise their own price

                                  172]]></page><page Index="61"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

               20. JEALOUSY, HATRED

• If we did not forgive to trespassers by prayer Our
  Father, we condemn ourselves

• Worse than an unjust person is the one who envies
  him

• Where the lie rules, hatered is immesuarable
• Jealousy and hatred are shackles on the human

  mind
• More envious of a person are those malicious

  people who know them better
• A jealous man is in great distress if he is not able

  to surpass someone’s prestige
• Belittling is also a dishonor
• He who does not tend towards the truth is not

  delighted to hear it
• He who does not aspire to love, easily finds a reason

  to hate
• The one who hates is not aware how big and

  dangerous his burden is
• Hatred is the path to eternal martyrdom

                                  173]]></page><page Index="62"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The disparaging hate is the lowest anti-human
  characteristic

• The underestimating hatred is the cause of many
  disrespects and crimes

• The underestimating hatred establishes death
  camps, too

• Chauvinism is a safe way to make enemies
• Chauvinists have a strong unconscious „skill“ to

  disgust many people with what is good

                                  174]]></page><page Index="63"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

         21. MISFORTUNE, EVIL, MALICE

• If an evil and good are mixed that makes it evil
• If an insane person begets an insane person, it is

  the culmination of misfortune
• Disorder in happiness is a welcome to misfortune
• The rule of justice without Christian morals is the

  scepter of the devil’s rule
• It is a huge spiritual mistake to say that you cannot

  see someone with your eyes
• Where the rich ones rule – opponents of the justice

  of the Lord tailor laws and the state is like their
  property
• Demons teach people to do evil deeds, but later
  they torture them in hell

• There are times when the people become so spoiled
  that good can be hard to find

• Gifts given for deception are like poisons
• Devil is where alcohol is poured
• Mean people live by means of taking away from

  other people
• By disregarding Lord’s words and life experience

  all generations are on the wrong path

                                  175]]></page><page Index="64"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• It is the evil’s trap that everyone should become
  one people without our Lord Jesus Christ

• The evil ones are not satisfied with the buried
  hatchet

• The evil ones called the left side to be something
  progressive in order to despise the right side of
  the Lord’s glory

• Impudence is called refinement by the evil

• It is a great evil when foul people become models
  and authorities of people

• Devil cannot be won by means of evil, but thus it
  can be served

• The abuse of thy neighbor is the culmination of
  dishonesty

• The villainous soul is nourished by abusing the
  just and the vulnerable

• Evil ideology makers and powers that be are the
  source of the most dangerous waters and winds

• The evil can be recognized by their company

• Both fortune-tellers and sorcerers are devil’s
  company

• Woe be to those whom reprobates bend to their will

                                  176]]></page><page Index="65"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• He who laughs at another person’s distress has a
  spiteful soul

• The one who does not want the Lord to be his
  shepherd has the devil as his guide

• The one who embraces the democracy of evil
  powerful people, appeals his own excavation

• He who underestimates the powers of evil, it befalls
  him

• When evil ideas come in the people’s minds, then
  wailing and screaming cover the ruins

• When you put evil on evil, then all the gates of
  hell are open

• When the evil multiply, then they point at the
  righteous with their finger

• Lying and disfavor are the will of the devil

• False and distorted right is a very powerful hope
  to the evil people especially to those in authority

• A beautiful but evil woman is a dove with a
  poisonous snake’s temperament

• The following state can be found in the people -
  there always comes the time of ruckus and scramble
  somewhere

• Multinational manipulators and radical natio-
  nalists are the most dangerous malicious people.

                                  177]]></page><page Index="66"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The discord of the oppressed is a great support to
  their tormentors

• In a mean and mysterious way, evil seed enters
  the people

• Rewarding for crimes makes the beast more
  dangerous

• Nationalities are misused by malicious people

• Some inventors of evils and deceptions regretfully
  talk about wolves’ times which they have produced
  themselves

• The worst blackmailers are the ones who create
  the conditions for blackmail, and then torture in
  troubles

• Only the immoral handle the stick of inhumanity

• Justification of drinking by life misfortunes is a
  deception

• This world is more and more the possession of the
  powerful and the executioners

• Those who do not forgive with their hearts do not
  have the love of God

• This world also bears the desert name

• Arrogance in rule, knowledge, career and the false
  prophets put everything they could to the evil’s hand

                                  178]]></page><page Index="67"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Help with mockery is not help but destruction

• A politically correct term for a malice is a division
  among people

• Foul people who bear academic titles are the most
  dangerous malefactors

• Showing lack of morals for fun is the preaching
  of evil

• Altercations are seeds that satan sows, and they
  grow the fastest

• The evil do not give the right to others from all
  kinds of inhumane reasons

• Mocking Christian virtues is one way of turning
  away from God

• Digging through someone else’s business is the
  same as evil seeking the devil

• Ridicule and gossip create hatred and lead to crime

• Radical nationalists are chauvinists

• The more life comforts, the more lie among people

• The more someone lies, the more they are under
  the influence of evil spirit

• He who is ruled by evil plans evil

• Malice is to the devil one of the dearest deeds

                                  179]]></page><page Index="68"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Woe unto the ones whose enemies are happy

• Hardly anything can be explained to those who
  are full of force and disrespect

• Killing in the name of God is an attack on God

• A troublemaker breaks into someone else’s house
  with a club to allegedly put order among family
  members

• Instead of help and compassion, a person is often
  given the conviction from another person

• The evil have always been protected by the laws of
  the powerful ones

• In television programs the contents are mostly
  satanic

• Bidders and takers of immorals are in a vicious circle

• Almost everything is misleading and easily ruined
  in the evil’s world

• School was created for human benefit, but if it is
  led by arrogance, then it is for the misfortune of
  the many

• The evil tread on everything apart from the terrible

• The more determined the wrong upbringing, the
  harder and more painful the recovery

                                  180]]></page><page Index="69"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

     22. INSANITY, RASHNESS, STUPIDITY

• When people „sleep“ , the sowers of the chaff gloat
• Unwanted consequences are certain if the respect

  is shown to the one who does not deserve it
• Groundless foreboding is insanity
• Insane and disgraced people respect shameful

  things
• It is insane to laud those who bear titles no matter

  what their orientation is
• Working fast and thinking fast usually have the

  same results
• Insolence is an inseparable ingredient of the evil

  spirit
• Impudent and insane people don’t need a reason

  for the argument
• Human insanity is so great that even one Sodom

  and one Gomorrah are not a sufficient warning
• Belief in the rightness of the teachings that are not

  blessed is actually disobedience of Lord
• The guiding principle in the behaviour of evil

  powers that be is to trip the just and kill them

                                  181]]></page><page Index="70"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• It is the saddest and the most stupid thing when
  the end defies infinity

• Acting like the powerful and the wise some of the
  envious ones are suffering for it

• If some died younger, they would leave better
  memories

• A long-lasting and wrong schooling destroys mind

• Due to the feelings of superiority and impunity
  proud reprobates do not confess to the sins of theirs

• Only insane people blame Lord for the conse-
  quences of their curse

• He who thinks to know everything, has something
  tangled in his mind

• Those who get used to the demonic slavery have
  their stomach as the only measurement of good
  and evil

• He who does not celebrate holidays with the
  blessed food and drinks desecrates God’s glory

• He who does not believe in God is fit to be neither
  a parent nor a friend

• He who does not have Lord in their heart is most
  interested in the truth they find suitable

• He who finds God’s words repulsive is close to the
  devil

                                  182]]></page><page Index="71"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Crazy people put on themselves wood and rocks
  to help themselves

• Pronancing a mad man as a smart one does not
  please God

• Uncontrolled rudeness is open madness

• Some gobbledegook, and then they wonder in bile
  why the listeners do not understand them

• Some guardians’ Spiritual places and arms are
  empty

• The unwise people think that the aggressive
  national boasters are righteous people

• It is good for the uninitiated some of the injustices
  as well if they do not know the true justice

• Those who protect themselves from danger should
  not pay attention to those who mock it

• Ordinary people often desecrate looking up to the
  bodily theorizing

• Tainted leaderships create temptations and
  multiply the paths of lawlessness

• A drunkard is a good example of what one should
  not be like

• A draft in the mind does not care for explanations

• The one who needs more time to notice what has
  been stinging for a long time is poorly reasonable

                                  183]]></page><page Index="72"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• A self-seeking person thinks that some people are
  nice to them because of their ‘high value’

• It is terribly unreasonable and a failure to ask for
  a good opinion from a teacher of injustice

• Our own hands are often the most valuable and
  everything is easy to do with the others’ hands

• All kinds of things are called culture in the evil
  and unwise world

                                  184]]></page><page Index="73"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

       23. IDLENESS, IMPUDENCE, THEFT

• If you they are not afraid of someone, the malicious
  ones would „take the life“ from a naive good man

• If a negligent person overlooks small errors, bigger
  errors can become „small matters“ in time

• Insolence is a murderer of love
• Impudence breaks the neck of well being
• An impudent fool boasts even with righteous

  imprisonment
• Spiritual misery would eventually want to bestride

  its friend
• Those who do not want to work or collaborate

  make the biggest snags in families
• An additional humiliation is when a conman is

  even mocking their victims

• Debasements and offences are a just cause for the
  vain

• Lending money to an idle man is help for his ruin
• Evil leaders and their assistants steal from their

  own people to provide for their descendants’ future

                                  185]]></page><page Index="74"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• There are some people who, instead of showing
  gratitude, break the borrowed thing when they
  no longer need it

• When the haughty become arrogant, their
  subordinates curse the day they were born on

• When it comes to the thievery the term alienation
  is the encouraging of theft

• The one who does not admire drunkard’s boasting
  and insolence in his disfavor falls

• He who has a tail, sews a tail on others

• The one who treats a bad man too well, when the
  treat is left out, they will be able to speak badly
  of him

• What kind of evil will be shown, mostly depends
  on the inheritance, ignorance and rudeness

• The one who had not stolen something, but then
  repented for not stealing it, has no human stability

• Robbery is a kind of snatching away or a little more
  shyly or a little more fearfully

• Rascals are endless holes if they can steal without
  consequences

• Some evil turns of mind seem to not be able to wait
  to show their inhumane characteristics

                                  186]]></page><page Index="75"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Idleness is a goody of hunger
• The inconsiderate ones do not feel welcome if they

  are prevented from doing damage
• Humiliation is rudeness and shamelessness
• The scoffer has difficulty in bridling his insolent

  language
• Those who mock others like the victims vulnerable

  in defence the most
• It is shattering when the state borrows from those

  who robbed it
• The prosecutor sees heavy offence if the one points

  to their bad deeds
• Mocking is the devil’s art
• Every crook bears the name of an immoral perso
• Stirring things up, is elementary school for thieves

                                  187]]></page><page Index="76"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

          24. WAR, FEAR, DESTRUCTION

• If villains show „calmness“, they are preparing to
  inflict more suffering and pain

• People who do all kinds of things and who flaunt
  their wealth strengthen the greedy and lure those
  who are moral to the wrong path

• It is hardest when even the basin where there once
  was a river is erased

• Drugs and alcohol are harbingers of death

• The evil state of humankind is clearly seen in the
  weapons it owns and in the wars it fights

• It is a crime to teach injustice
• Even if it is sometimes unavoidable, war is the

  foundation of evil
• Losing the sense of justice means losing the pledge

  of living
• When the common property is damaged and

  abused the father of precipice greatly rejoices
• He who is not afraid of God, is afraid of the

  authorities the most

                                  188]]></page><page Index="77"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Powerful evildoers destroy the countries and
  peoples in order to subjugate the entire world to
  liars

• The darkest evildoers are those who are convinced
  of their justice

• Foulness is a strong condition of the descendants’
  fall

• War is to the devils a saint and a brother
• Courage and foulness can be easily seen in war
• The more a man fears other men, the
• is more and more evil

                                  189]]></page><page Index="78"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

              25. THE GODLESS, SECTS

• If an atheist’s descendant is atheistic then they are
  freaks descended from freaks

• If a man is ruled only by instinct, then the health
  of their soul is destroyed

• Impious parents are enemies both to themselves
  and to their descendants

• The ungodly are in the symbol of the serpent
• The unbelievers do not believe in Resurrection

  and do not like repentance
• The unbelievers have a cheek to do everything

  they want
• Unscrupulous are those for whom neither common

  sense nor evidence is applicable
• Atheists consider Christian morality the worst

  nightmare
• Atheism is the key of misfortune
• Unbelievers find their lives unthinkable without

  lies and deception
• Ungodly inventors of human rights are working

  to extinguish Christian morality

                                  190]]></page><page Index="79"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Atheists are Babylon and Sodom of every age

• Unholy people can be classified into three sides

• The ungodly desecrate some truths by adapting
  them to their needs

• Godless political parties are demonic cells

• The godless have worshipped an evil mind and its
  achievements

• Atheistic ways finally lead to the eradication of
  the evil

• The godless one is a stranger

• Godless people are damned people

• The godless reigns abound with the planned
  immorality

• Works of dissension from God are demons’ food

• God’s apostates are irresistible architects and
  planners of evil

• The big players of immorality are the stars for the
  evil people

• By deceiving themselves and others, the ungodly
  replace love with folly

• The godless who are educated are mostly more
  dangerous than the godless who are not educated

                                  191]]></page><page Index="80"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Belief in the Lord in your own way is not a piety

• The main foothold of an evil spirit is in evil people
  from the higher class

• It is not important for the spiritually empty ones
  anything that it is not related to the exit section
  of their stomach

• Main reprobates and miscreants are gods of evil

• Demon’s servants lose an opportunity to become
  sons of peace and justice

• There are many of those who are venerated as
  saints by some people, but they are burning in hell

• Due to the unworthy in the family, the weeds have
  captured the land

• Evil moguls introduce disorder for easier theft
  and plunder

• The evil ones desire and find faults of the righteous
  ones in order to blemish them

• The evil mind is the product of evil spirit

• An evil mogul is materially rich but spiritually poor

• Evil moguls are blood thirsty

• The evil spirit is almost everywhere around us and
  it is within the many of us

                                  192]]></page><page Index="81"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Even the mention of the homeland where the
  famous bad man was born causes discomfort in
  people

• Even if they have been done good by an honest
  person, reprobates continue to cause them trouble

• Judah Iscariot is a simbol of false believers

• Jezavela represents ungodliness, a God-fearing path

• Cain’s followers are the godless

• When a pervert learns of the shames of the weak,
  he joins their company

• Who refuses healing, holds out their hands to
  illness

• The one who boasts of apostate behavior elevates
  nothingness

• He who does not oppose the demon’s slavery awaits
  a hellish fate

• When the spoiled talks most beautifully then one
  should be especially careful

• To those who are saved from the gentiles by the
  gang, the evil people are still superior

• He who understands, the unrighteous people
  mainly mark themselves

• There is an evil ghost in both the seeds and the
  graves of the reprobates

                                  193]]></page><page Index="82"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Liars insult common sense and oppose to the Holy
  Spirit

• Bad pious people can become the worst apostates
  from faith

• Human wickedness is the most devastating
  infection

• Many people are very quick to humiliate those
  who do them no harm

• Upside down signs and numbers are some of the
  distinguishing marks of belonging to satan

• It is the easiest to deceive a gullible friend

• Some do not even give what they intend to throw
  away but they make it unusable first

• There will be no peace or the God’s justice while
  the unbelievers are in charge

• God’s enemies cause lasting harm to those who
  believe them

• Insecurities and blackmail are regular actions of
  the evil people

• Some are convinced that they will be desacred by
  shaking hands, but they themselves are already
  sordid

• Those who deserve to be the least respected are
  the angriest at disrespect

                                  194]]></page><page Index="83"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The intolerance and avoidance of the Christian
  morality is opposition to the Lord

• Some so-called Christians act as if trouble and
  killing are an integral part of God’s faith

• Irredeemable are those who do not repent

• It is clear in the eyes of some people: “I am nobody
  and nothing who just wants to do everything bad.”

• Those who have no honor do not deserve respect

• Uncontrolled exposure to dangers is not in the
  spirit of piety

• Lack of the blessed love comes from the lack of belief

• The absence of human wickedness is increasingly
  perceived as a rational defect

• What makes the ungodly preach nonviolence is in
  the service of disorder

• Material things are both the beginning and the
  end to those who tend towards injustice

• Those who turn the torment into fornication are
  not better than torturers

• It is enjoyment to a corrupt person to abuse a weak
  one

• A reprobate sees disgrace in self-criticism

                                  195]]></page><page Index="84"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Loathsome living is a sure preparation for eternal
  death

• Loathsome and failed nation is every nation where
  the reputation is acquired by blasphemous life

• A crook’s gratitude whether it was or not, when it
  could not cause damage

• The perverts in power have found violence to be
  the most lucrative

• Reprobates and villains have taught lessons of ‘civil
  behaviour’ from times immemorial

• Corruption is a heart like crocodile swamp

• The cursed stamp on people is a sign of a spiritual
  bottom with no return.

• The closest in spirit to Judah Iscariot help the evil
  people in creating evil

• Ones will not become devotees because of the pan
  and ladle

• For lack of repentance, the beast is unleashed to
  the godless people

• Boasting of arrogant people is the dark reputation
  - destroyer of health and joy and a terrible ordeal
  for many

• More and more are those who get the devil’s
  dwelling even in their youth

                                  196]]></page><page Index="85"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Sects are communities of the fallen away from God
  whose founders are devils

• When the ungodly ones rule every age is very
  similar

• Sects and free builders are the advance guards of
  satan’s army

• Weak pious people prefer swords over prayer
• One should open one’s eyes wide because

  unbelievers call their injustice justice
• The defiant behavior of the evil ones also includes

  humiliating disgust
• To brand the antichrist’s seal on the head or the

  hand of people, is a certain entrance into eternal fire
• The united human waste tenaciously works towards

  smothering the God’s love
• Schooled evildoers are convinced that they are in

  many ways super humans
• The more godless people, the more temptation

                                  197]]></page><page Index="86"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                 26. MISCELLANEOUS

• If the sick one asks for prayers from someone from
  the church, and that person directs him to find
  another cure, he is acting the pious person badly

• If they might ask for the vulnerable person, those
  whose love has cooled do that for the sake of
  appearances

• If we started from ourselves first, we would not
  do injustice to others

• If a man doesn’t respect his own words, it is a
  hardship for others, and for him it is inevitable
  shame

• The insane one finds it funny to do evil, while the
  sensible man takes delight in wisdom (The Wisdom
  of Solomon 10. 23.)

• Quick ripening, makes for certain rotting

• Great human values are always a target for
  dishonest people

• Hospitality is not in murmuring but in gentleness
  and love

                                  198]]></page><page Index="87"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• By hospitality in their homes some greedy people
  endeavour to enhance their status

• Society would be happy if it were not for brothers
  disowning each other

• Good deeds honour ancestors while bad behaviour
  defames them

• A wicked man likes it when somebody does him
  good, but in his soul he feels bad that that person
  is noble

• The problem that you are avoiding constantly, is
  a fierce pursuer

• He who is carried away by someone else’s footsteps
  can fall into a pit

• Mockery and slander are spiritual treasures to
  wicked people

• For worthless people this or that loathsome
  authority is good

• The community of Goodness and benevolence is
  presumed, but it is not often concurent

• The temptation and the risk is to accept a
  descendant of the Church persecutor as a friend

• The wealthy one can be criticized by his own
  conscience if they gave to the poor more than
  intended

                                  199]]></page><page Index="88"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• And the last station has a continuation

• There can be immorality even among those in
  marriage

• Even dancing causes unchastity

• By emphasising their titles the irresponsible people
  can cloud retrogression

• He who is depraved very young, what can he be
  like at the end of his life

• If the Lord God could hear every prayer, everything
  would fail

• If an evil person’s soul could be opened like a book,
  some readers would run far away

• Great strength is useful, however, he who abuses
  it has an abysmal stone around their neck

• He who believes in God out of spite, will lose his
  faith with bile

• He who cannot talk without lying would better
  remain silent

• Shortsightedness is the most widespread flaw

• When a word remains in the thoughts for a while,
  it is much more tasteful

• He who tries to gain good by acting badly will fall
  into the hole they have dug for another

• He who pleases the insolent, will be met by thick
  thorns on the way

                                  200]]></page><page Index="89"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• If mean people praise your work, either it is not
  good or something is hidden behind it

• Whoever has known the truth, knows about the
  lie, which is good and which is evil

• Who lashes at the truth, will be lashed by lies

• New life will start when science and technology
  come to a spiritual bottom

• Who is able to help his neighbors, but does not
  want to, will be leashed of God’s help

• Who feels happy in ill-fated times, is carried by
  the devil, and he himself is carrying ignorance

• A naive benefactor expects gratitude even from
  the spiritual cripple

• Nice and good words are often left uncovered with
  what belongs to them

• People and times give birth to each other

• People are least sinful as babies, and at the end of
  life many are the most vicious

• Interpersonal collaboration should be fostered
  with great caution

• Many people would do good deeds only if they
  didn’t have any other choice

• There are not a lot of no way outs

                                  201]]></page><page Index="90"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Soft-hearted man is neither bad nor good, because
  he is prone to his own depersonalization

• Most people let it go to their head when they are
  praised

• Theorising and wisdom are not the same

• A believer finds it hard to get on with atheists
  just like a sober man finds it hard to get on with
  a drunkard

• Bad news is most eagerly brought by a bad man

• Many people carry their soul in the pockets

• The foundations of evil rest on imprudence and
  impudence

• Partiality brings many troubles

• He who has the most deformed soul is the one who
  is sorry to put an effort into their most valuable
  necessity

• Everything belongs to someone, everything
  belongs to others

• Some people would do well to others just if it costs
  nothing

• Peace is not if there are only no shootings nor is
  war only where there are

                                  202]]></page><page Index="91"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• One should not persecute the persecutor’s
  descendants

• The teeth chatter not only from the cold, but from
  other things as well

• The most dangerous ones are those in community
  with the chiefs of the authorities

• Wisdom and courage can deal with troubles in the
  best possible way

• An invisible hand leads you to coincidence

• Distrust could be a trap of danger, confusion and
  discomfort

• Unfair distiction will make someone haughty
  rather than teach them

• The unjust will not accept a good piece of advice
  from someone who is not notable

• A low-life listens secretly

• Depravities are wrapped in the most various ways

• It is not good to count how many good things you
  have done to your neighbor

• Trouble can serve as a cure, too

• Levity often contains immoralities

• Lack of morals is shameful to believers whereas
  the unbelievers consider it an achievement

                                  203]]></page><page Index="92"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Some think it is right to take something away from
  the pauper after they had earlier helped them

• Unthoughtfullness creates injustice, bile and
  quarrelling

• It’s not a desert where there are few people but
  where evil spirits are the leaders

• The wheat is not in the lie nor is the chaff in the
  truth

• It is not charity in a mixture of help and hindrance
  but in helping and no hindrance

• Generous people who give what they intend to
  throw away are not the worst

• Through the absence of some difficult experience
  a depraved person becomes more depraved

• He who defends honor, deserves every honor

• Response to criticism by those without self-
  criticism is impudence

• Evil news bearers burn even the bonfires

• There is a short step between an evil word and an
  evil deed

• From a wish, even an evil starts

• Honourable people and reprobates can hardly
  understand one another

                                  204]]></page><page Index="93"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Spiteful spouse is the destroyer of familiarity and
  love

• The true picture of the world can have the person
  who does not flatter, and neither is flattered

• Professional tidiness does not necessarily mean
  morality

• Justice is a fair way away from those who go down
  the unblessed path

• An empty look is total blindness

• Тhe evil people will be fooled by the knowledge
  and wisdom of theirs

• Fasting is a rein and a broom for the soul and body

• An evil person can awake if they are hit by an
  Almighty Hand

• Reprobates are those who are the most unrestrained
  in tarnishing just people

• The wheat and the chaff are two true standards of
  measurement

• Work without love is deficient

• A word can sometimes be the most dangerous
  weapon

• Rarely can an honourable person meet a spiteful
  person without the latter beginning to stink

                                  205]]></page><page Index="94"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• All sorts of God’s apostates easily unite against those
  who venerate Saints

• Everything has a father

• There is less and less Christian love among people,
  and there is less response thereto

• By living our life we invigorate our happiness or
  we sabotage it by being deceived

• Poorly organised end up their works pell-mell

• The insane value those who drink a lot and fight
  a lot

• Evil powers do not have the sigh of martyrdom

• Poor character is able to bully even an ill person

• It is satanic to think like this: it is important that
  everything is good for me, but who cares about
  others

• The one who forgives others constantly, can
  encourage repentance

• Self-praise stinks with filthiness

• Every lawlessness is a lie if the laws are not in
  breach and injustice

• Liars are valued by the poorly reasonable people
  and the credulous

                                  206]]></page><page Index="95"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• A small heart lacks in mercy

• Gossipers and slanderers take off the masks from
  their faces

• It is sad to hear the dishonoured people swear to
  what they do not have

• Feelings about something and self-confidence can
  be very tricky

• Learning, forgiving and long-suffering look for
  their own limits

• Abstention from admitting not having knowledge,
  is running away from knowledge

• In the wish and the strength of will there is power

• He who tells the truth in bad times, can be seen
  as a mad person

• A sufferer is a benefactor in evil times

• Defending oneself from oneself is honorable and
  heroic

• In these times infected with evil, the illusion of
  knowing everything drowns a better tomorrow
  even for our children

• The one is in conflict with oneself and with the
  truth if they talk that they are devoted, but they
  mock even the pious ones

                                  207]]></page><page Index="96"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• In a tidal wave of depravity all values have come
  into question

• Praise is usually for the earthly glory and other
  selfish reasons

• Honor is the proud feathers of man
• An executor is not only the one who holds a sword

  over the head of the convicted
• If you create something by means of lying, stealing

  or violence, it will come to ruin
• Whispering hides sickness, love, sorrow and

  treacherous intentions
• It is inhumane to give something bad as a present

  to others
• What is not recommendable for the young is no

  good for the old either
• What is evil to the righteous people, it is good to

  the unrighteous people if it is not their concern

                                  208]]></page><page Index="97"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                      27. MESSAGES

• O give thanks unto the Lord; for he is good: for his
  mercy endureth forever (Psalm 136. 1.)

• Praise ye the Lord, praise ye the name of the Lord;
  praise him, o ye servants of the Lord (Psalm 135. 1.)

• Ask, and it shall be given you; seek, and ye shall find;
  knock, and it shall be opened unto you (Matthew
  7. 7.)

• The Prophet Jeremiah 17. 5, 7.
• If the evil persistently sets in, love goes away.
• The blessed education is desecrated if the educated

  are spoilt
• It is more God pleasing that the name of the Lord’s

  Eden has no national sign
• Ungodliness in schools is a special betrayal of piety
• The evil rules without the God’s truth and justice
• There is no sincere regret without empathy
• Desperation is one of the certain indicators of life

  aimlessness
• It is better to come nearer God when He mercifully

  points to the evil in us

                                  209]]></page><page Index="98"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• If there is no repentance in the heart there is no
  peace

• By running away from Lord one gets to precipice

• Multiple bullies and traditional naughties
  understand only their intent

• Religious and material differences degrade
  familiarity the most

• Our Lord in the manger means Food and Drinks
  for vigour and Life of the sheep of His pasture

• The Lord’s Church and wars are in contradiction,
  it is foolish to bind them

• Where there is a great number of the dishonoured
  people there is no political responsibility there

• The globalistic way of bringing up children throws
  the Solomon’s wisdom under the feet

• By Lord’s word everything blessed is renewable

• Lord administers justice among people through
  His Saints and establishes the just court

• If everyone has their own truth, there is no Lord’s
  truth there

• Where there is no Christian goodness, everything
  is bland

• Whether the Earth rotates or not is not a matter
  of the Church

                                  210]]></page><page Index="99"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Some would better understand Lord’s spirituality
  if their ‘ancestor had not been a monkey’

• „A good believer“, but a bad penitent is not the
  righteous one

• The life bearer is older than an egg from which
  the life originates

• The Sodom rainbow defies Lord by desecrating
  the name of His glory

• So the virtues would perish faster „democrats“
  have proclaimed anarchy as freedom

• The state of life is a thorn in the eye of those who
  work for the state of death

• The state is just as much righteous as its leaders
  repent of sin

• The Iron Sceptre is on the verge of being used

• Human tragedies are inevitable, because people
  do not obey God’s Ten Commandments

• Those who employ the desecrated school
  knowledge contribute the most to the existence
  of irresponsible authorities

• If you do not care for your soul and your
  descendants, you live only while you are alive

                                   211]]></page><page Index="100"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Evil authorities fool peoples in all sorts of ways
  and they even found false churches

• Evil moguls are adversaries of the bare existence
  of the many

• Evil moguls have a wish to keep as many people in
  subservience and inquietude as possible

• By misusing the name of the Holy People
  supportively they create misconceptions

• It is well known how the evil ended in Egypt; they
  will end that way everywhere again

• Evil are those who call freedom a state in which
  there is anguish to fall asleep in their own home

• And the parent will spit on the benefactor under
  the influence of a bad conscience

• One of the worst characteristics of many is the
  lack of love towards everything that is not theirs

• It is miserable and sad for the pious when devilish
  people live mixed with them

• He who is not in god-pleasing justice does not
  belong to a peaceful folks

• The Book of Life is the Celestial City where there
  is no sorrow nor crying

                                  212]]></page><page Index="101"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The one who is especially appealing to the Lord
  knows who the Heavenly Father

• When it comes to the justice, the atheists are not
  worthy to be the authorities

• When a reasonable man seeks reconciliation,
  irredeemable one gossips about them

• When the actions are not called what they truly
  are, it strengthens the devil’s will

• He whose mind is pillaged by the devil, it becomes
  his shovel and broom

• When a “stranger” tries to be as good as possible,
  he has evil intentions

• When Lord frees the Sion’s slavery, the harvest of
  the earthly wheat ensues

• When there are no signs of faith the Lord mentions,
  the breakdown appears

• If people would compete in good as hard as in evil,
  the Heaven would be more certain

• It would be a trap for the one who is healed by the
  Lord if they did not repent

• The ring-leaders of lawlessness and disorder seek
  the “reform” of Church laws, and statutes

                                  213]]></page><page Index="102"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• He who knows the difference between the truth
  and lies speaks righteously

• The one who sees the earthly theorizing
  benevolently will not see the keys to the Heavenly
  Kingdom

• When relying on earthly rot you put it on yourself

• Whoever opposes the dishonorables because of a
  vulnerable one, the damned try to grind him too

• The one who considers the godless crowd as God’s
  people critisize the God’s glory

• He who puts the earthly first rather than the
  spiritual, has a weak faith and hope in Lord

• Dandysm and seductive clothing is in service of
  moral destruction

• A bad company influences neglect of bonds with
  the righteous

• It is insane to beg someone in the name of God if
  they do not acknowledge God

• Spiritual wisdom contains easier and deep secrets

• Bodily theorizing is the contrary to the Christian
  virtues

• New Heaven and New Earth will be free from the
  godless people

                                  214]]></page><page Index="103"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Not everything that resembles depravity is an
  intention, negligence and ignorance

• It is not pleasing to God to have descendants whose
  way is doing all sorts of things

• Injustice is a builder of hate and a destroyer of love

• One cannot become rich on the foundation of the
  blessed truth and justice

• One cannot expect good from those who are not
  repentant nor forgiving

• The most vicious are those who destroy the state
  of life

• National haughtiness badly influences the believers

• Prayer is not the waste of time, but the misfortune
  is where there is no prayer to the Lord at all

• It is wrong to say that a man is adorned by the place

• Do not behave properly only when someone is
  watching you

• It is not an honor to be a prophet in their own
  homeland because of human malice

• Pious people and others live on earth

• No one will be saved on the Lord’s Judgement Day
  by their lack of belief but by their faith

                                  215]]></page><page Index="104"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• The New World Order is a kingdom of saboteurs
  of justice, peace, and freedom

• One advice of the satan is: take everything that
  life offers

• We cannot allow our passions to plan our offspring

• The poor do not attack the authorities but the
  unbelieving authorities have long been harassing
  and killing us

• It is not good to remove or move the night guard

• The godless cities burnt by heavenly fire will have
  no salvation

• From the threatening feeling of the Lord’s
  desolation there comes a fear that remains forever

• The pious and the ungodly ones are two worlds

• Piety and depravity are mutually exclusive

• An honest person who starts from himself should
  beware of surprises

• An honourable person wishes that all people be
  like him, while a reprobate values those who are
  similar to him the most

• The filthy one is not cruel only towards some
  people, but towards many of them

                                  216]]></page><page Index="105"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Through the false believers the evil influence even
  the repentant Home

• Test yourself as you like, but not to someone’s
  disadvantage

• Breaking the God’s will is damnation

• Pacification does not suit the Damned because
  God is in peace

• Even the story about a fly can lead to the mockery
  of truth

• The piety is not lack of our sins recognition
• Colorful manipulators and their henchmen are

  the creators of the new world order
• Love of pleasure deranges the mind
• Poor hope to the Lord are the ones who both

  believe and do not believe
• Poorly reasonable often see the justice in capability
• Broken cross is a sign of failure for those who show

  it like that

• One should do good with the faith in God and not
  expect gratitude from people

• If you fast, your marriage bed should fast as well

                                  217]]></page><page Index="106"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

• Soon the wheat will be separated from the chaff
  for those who be in the Lord’s blessing

• In vain we knock on the Imperial Gate if the Lord
  sees unrepentant brigands in us

• Streets in which Christian simplicity has no price
  do not belong to a kind city

• In absence of self-criticism a man is on a trackless
  area

• The evil hate and persecute the Lord’s Church as
  it is the obstacle on their way of doing all kinds
  of things

• The pure should only have their feet washed since
  they walk on the desecrated grounds

• Frequent workers’ rights are - to be used, to be spit
  upon and to keep quiet

• The stable in which our Lord Jesus Christ was born
  represents this world

                                  218]]></page><page Index="107"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

              28. PRAYERS TO GOD

                      PRAYER 1

Lord God, Father, have mercy upon us and save
for us Thy holiness, restore and save your nation
from violence and injustice of evil members of
higher class, of the beast’s temper and claws, of
the false prophets, and of every other evil, misery
and disease. Save Thy nation from the satan marks.

Lord, Thou showed great wonders to the world
through Thy Sacred, and it is known that you can
do anything. Thou managed with the heart of
Pharaoh, for every human heart is in Thy hand.
Propitiate the emperors of the earth, and make
the heart of folkgents soften towards Thy holiness
and towards Thy people.

Lord, pour Thy mercy on Thy Vineyard by Thy
great goodness, sheltering its inside and outside by
unconquerable fence from its opponents, so that
no one can do any harm to it, so that its drudges
can in Thy peace, and in love and joy celebrate the
only venerable and the glorious name of Thy.

Glory to the Father and to the Son and to the Holy
Spirit, both now and in all ages, Amen! Alleluia!

                                219]]></page><page Index="108"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      220]]></page><page Index="109"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                      PRAYER 2

Lord God, Our Father, for a long time and in cruel
manner the godless, doing bad things, show their
evil face and vicious nature of theirs towards Thy
male and female servants, crushing and sabotaging
Thy Holy Church, for Thy opponents are bothered
with all what is for the common welfare and what
bears life and peace in itself.

Have mercy and help us, for the evil people rush
relentlessly to Thy truth. Protect and liberate all
Thy servants from all sorts of their tyranny.

Lord, do not let us, for the powerful of this world
are trying to make everything that is good and
useful for our souls nonsensical and headlong.

Please heal the diseased human right so that the
justice is not mocked by the powerful evildoers.

Lord help, for the tyranny is unbearable any more.

Merciful Lord, determine Thy nation in Thy prayers
and make them be the joy to all of us and be as
regular as the meals are to people and give us Thy
fear into our hearts so that we never depart from
thee, and so that we can conduct and hold to Thy
doctrine and Thy laws.

                                221]]></page><page Index="110"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

Have mercy for nation of Thy, and purify and
regenerate all Thy creation.
Glory to the Father and the Son and the Holy
Spirit, both now and in all ages, Amen! Alleluia!

                                222]]></page><page Index="111"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                      PRAYER 3
Oh Lord, my God, Thy unworthy servant prays
in tears to Thee that there is neither a single lying
mouth nor a single thieving hand.
These are my great desires, and Thou Lord, the
only hope, comfort and joy of mine.
Glory to the Father and the Son and the Holy
Spirit, both now and in all ages, Amen! Alleluia!

                                223]]></page><page Index="112"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      224]]></page><page Index="113"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

                      PRAYER 4
Lord, have mercy and give eternal peace to the
souls of Joko, Danica and Milorad.
Lord, have mercy; Lord, have mercy; Lord, have
mercy!
Glory to the Father and the Son and the Holy
Spirit, both now and in all ages, Amen! Alleluia!

                                225]]></page><page Index="114"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES
                      226]]></page><page Index="115"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

    Our Lord Jesus Christ:
  And behold, I am come
quickly, and my reward is
with me, to give to every man
according as work shall be.

               (Revelation 22. 12.)

                           227]]></page><page Index="116"><![CDATA[Kosto Jokov Albijanić – WITH OPEN EYES

     Косто Јоков Албијанић
     ОТВОРЕНИХ ОЧИЈУ

         Уредник (editor in chief):
           Радомир Уљаревић
          Издавачи (publichers):

    Штампар Макарије, Београд
       Ободско слово, Подгорица

 Херцеговина издаваштво, Требиње
           Тираж (circulation):
                     2022.
             Штампа (print):

       Ободско слово, Подгорица

                 ЦИП:

                      228]]></page></pages></Search>